OK, let's pick up where we left off and define the event handler in function.
So copy it.
And let's make a comment here.
Initializes the wi fi application.
Event handler for Wi-Fi and IP events.
And this function will be static void of function name.
And it takes no parameters.
And he will say event loop for the wife driver.
Now, let's SPRO check.
ESP event loop creates.
And choose create default.
And next, we'll create the event handler for the connection.
And then we'll need an ESP event handler instance type.
And call it instance fire event.
And now copy the instance type.
And paste it.
And now here, call it instance IP event.
And next, SPRO check.
ESG event handler.
Instance registered.
And the event base is Wi-Fi event.
The event ID is ESP event, any ID.
And the event handler is a reference to the function name, which we'll call wi fi app event handler.
The handle, the arguments are no.
And instance will be a reference to instance why fire event?
An now copied this line.
And placed below.
And now we want IP events.
And the ID is the same.
The handler is the same, and this is no.
And change the reference to instance, IP event.
And that's it.
So now we need to define this event handler.
So let's come here.
And let's comment, Wi-Fi application event handler.
And the first parameter ARG is data.
Aside from event data.
That is passed to the handler.
When it is called.
And the second parameter event base.
Is the base aid of the event to register the handler for?
And the third parameter event, I.D..
Is the idea of the event to register the handler for?
And the fourth parameter event data.
Is the event data?
So this function is static void.
WI fi app event handler and the first parameter is a void point to ARG.
The next parameter is ESP event based type.
And it's even based.
The next is in 30 to.
Event ID.
And the last is a void pointer event data.
Then here will say if.
Event bass.
Is a Wi-Fi event.
Then we'll switch.
Event ID.
And then now we'll open a case.
For Wi-Fi event.
AP start.
And now let's log the message for this case with ESP log info.
Our tag.
And the Messages Wi-Fi event app start.
And then include a break.
And this wi fi event here is just one of many.
So come here and look over the type of events you can include and just create them in the event handler
and you can handle them in your application.
So let's copy this event.
And we'll create another.
For Wi-Fi app, stop.
And now let's create another event.
For a start.
And now let's do the same.
Stay connected.
Now, let's do another one.
For stay disconnected.
Let's come back up here and make another one.
For AP, stay connected.
And now let's make another one.
For a stay disconnected.
All right, good, so that should cover our basic needs for now.
And now let's come down here and say else if.
Event bass.
Is an IP event.
Then say Switch event ID.
And let's create a new case here.
IP event FDA.
Gut IP.
And now let's S.P. log info.
The message.
For the state, got IP event.
And then let's break.
All right, so that's it for this one.
Now we can define the default by faith in IT function.
And let's comment.
Initializes the TCP stack.
In default Wi-Fi configuration.
And it's static void of function, and it's void.
And first of all, same initialize the TCP stack.
And ESPN check.
The speed net if.
Init function.
And next, we'll do the default wi fi config.
And I'll just mention that operations must be in this order.
Now we need an instance of the wi fi in it config type.
And call it white, fly in it, config.
And initialize it with wi fi in it config.
Default function.
And so here, espera check.
SPV, I fight in it.
And pass a reference to this white fight in it config.
And the next bill, SB air check.
S.P. Rifai said storage as Wi-Fi, storage RAM.
And now let's grab our network interface object.
And let's initialize it.
Using ISP net if.
Create default white by.
Stay.
Then let's initialize the AP object.
Using ESG net if.
Create default.
WI fi AP.
Great, that's it.
Now, let's create the soft AP config.
And let's comment.
Configures the wi fi access point settings.
And designs the static IP.
To the soft AP.
And it's a static void.
WI fi apps off the AP config.
And it's void.
Right now, let's say soft API, Wi-Fi Access Point configuration.
And now create the Wi-Fi config structure.
And call it AP config.
And he will need to specify the access point config.
Like so.
And then set the aside.
To our wi fi AP a suicide.
Next, set the seaside length.
Using Stalin of wi fi.
AP A suicide.
And then the password.
Will be our wi fi app password.
And that's the channel.
Will be our wi fi app channel.
And then SSD hidden.
His wife by AP, a suicide.
Hidden.
In authorization mode.
We'll use Wi-Fi off.
WPA two.
And now Max connections.
We'll be wi fi AP.
Max connections.
And then beacon interval.
We'll be wi fi, AP Beacon interval.
This should be actually be a comma here.
Now let's.
Configure, DHP.
For the access point.
Now, let's create an instance of the ESPN net if IP info type.
And call it AP IP info.
And now let's set this.
API info.
Two zero for the size of the API info.
All right, because we want this cleared out first.
And now call ESPN net if.
DHC Post-up.
And that's where our ESG net if app.
And this function stops the DHP server that we want to do this before making any DHC related updates.
And again, that's fraud, and that if AP object you.
And we'll say.
Musk called his first.
Because we want to call this first before making any changes.
And then let's call Annette Piton.
And specify if I get.
Then why fi a pipe?
With a reference to our API info.
IP address.
Now I'll say here, assign access points, static IP.
Gateway and netmask.
And what this function does is, is it converts an internet address and it's standard text format into
its numeric binary form.
And that's what we want here.
So now let's copy this line and then let's do the same for Gateway.
And Gateway here.
And then again, for netmask.
And that mask you.
All right, Greg.
So now let's espero check.
ESPN net, if said IP and phone.
And specify our ESPN at if AP and a reference to our AP IP info.
And now SPRO, check.
ESPN that if.
DHC GPS start.
And again, use our air speed net if AP object.
And to you, I'll just comment.
Statically configures the network interface.
And this one.
Starts the AP.
DHC server.
For connecting stations.
E.g., your mobile device.
And now let's espero check.
ESP set mode.
And the mode we want is wifey mode.
AP.
Stay.
And here we are.
Setting the mode as access point.
Station mode.
And then let's SPRO check.
ESB Wi-Fi.
Said config.
For ISP interface.
Wi-Fi access point.
And reference the AP config.
And here.
We've set our configuration.
And then ESPN check.
ESP wi fi said bandwidth.
For a Wi-Fi interface access point.
And use our wi fi app bandwidth.
And that's where our default bandwidth.
20 megahertz.
And again, let's SPRO check.
ESB Wi-Fi.
Set power, safe save.
To our white five star power save.
And that's our power save set to none.
Which we had previously defined you in the head of file.
OK, so now I'll just inspect this.
This looks good.
And up here, this message.
This should be disconnected.
So let's log it correctly.
And so just be sure of that.
And then now this should be static.
OK, now let's build to be sure, there's no errors.
OK, that looks good.
So let's finalize and test this in the next lesson.